Now, I mentioned this term before,
我之前提到过的一个说法是
but all this code that we wrote, when we hit this compile button,
我们在这里写下的全部代码，当我们点击这个编译(Compile)按钮时
it compiles it down to the EVM or the Ethereum virtual machine.
它其实是在 EVM 或者说以太坊虚拟机(Ethereum Virtual Machine)上编译的
Don't worry too much about what this means.
暂且不用太纠结它到底是什么意思
EVM is a standard of how to deploy smart contracts to Aetherium like blockchains.
EVM 就是如何往以太坊这样的区块链上部署智能合约的一个标准
And any blockchain that implements a type of EVM. You can deploy solidity code to
并且任何实现某种 EVM 的区块链，你都可以把 solidity 代码部署上去
some examples of EVM compatible blockchains
这里举一些与 EVM 兼容的区块链的例子
are going to be avalanche, Phantom, and polygon.
比如，Avalanche, Fantom, Polygon
Since these are EVM compatible,
它们与 EVM 是兼容的
this means we can write our solidity code, and deploy to these blockchains,
意思就是我们可以把编写的 solidity 代码，部署到这些区块链上
which again, I'll show you later on how to add these new networks into your Metamask.
不用担心，之后我就会展示如何为你的 MetaMask 添加新的网络
And then how to deploy them.
以及如何部署它们
Let's do a quick recap of our first smart contract.
让我们快速回顾一下我们的首个智能合约
And then you should actually take a break, maybe get some ice cream or coffee
然后你就可以休息一下了，来点冰淇淋或者咖啡
because you absolutely deserve it. Congratulations.
你绝对配得上获得这份奖励，再次对你表示祝贺
The first thing you always need to do in your smart contracts is tell solidity,
在你的智能合约中你总是要做的第一件事就是告诉 solidity
what version of solidity that you're going to be using.
你正在使用的是哪个版本的 solidity
And additionally, you want to add an spdx license identifier,
并且你还得添加一个 SPDX-License-Identifier
then you have to create your contract object and name your contract.
接着你就要创建你的合约对象并为它命名
The contract in solidity is similar to a class in other programming languages,
solidity 中的合约(contract)就类似于其他编程语言中的类(class)
and everything inside the squiggly brackets is a part of that contract.
并且花括号里的所有内容都是该合约的组成部分
There are many different types in solidity
solidity 有许多不同的数据类型
like unsigned integer 256, Boolean, string, bytes 32, etc.
例如无符号256位整型(unsigned integer 256)，布尔值(Boolean)，字符串(string)，32位字节(bytes 32)，等等
If we want to create a new type, we can create what's called a struct in solidity.
如果我们想创建一种新类型，我们可以在 solidity 中创建一个所谓的结构体(struct)
You can create arrays or lists in solidity,
你可以在 solidity 中创建数组(array)或者说列表(list)
you can create dictionaries, or what's called mappings in solidity or hash tables,
你可以创建字典(dictionarie)，或者称为 solidity 中的映射(mapping)，或是叫哈希表(hash table)也可以
which when you give it a key, it'll spit out the value that that key represents.
当你给它一个键(key)时，它就会返回与该键对应的值(value)
We can create functions in solidity
我们可以在 solidity 中创建函数
that modify the state of the blockchain.
以修改区块链的状态
We can also create functions in solidity that don't modify the state of the blockchain
我们也可以在 solidity 中创建不修改区块链状态的函数
view in pure functions, don't modify by the state of a blockchain,
view 和 pure 函数就是不修改区块链状态的函数
we also can specify different data locations in our functions,
我们也可以在函数中指定不同的数据位置(data location)
called data and memory mean that that data is only temporary
calldata 和 memory 的意思就是该数据只是临时数据
and will only exist for the duration of the function.
它们只在函数运行期间存在
Storage variables are permanent and stay there forever.
storage 变量则是永久存在的
function parameters can't be stored variables
函数的参数不能是 storage 变量
because they're only going to exist for the duration of the function.
因为它们只能存在于函数运行期间
All the solidity code that we work with,
这就是我们所使用的所有 solidity 代码
when we hit Compile, it actually compiles down to this Aetherium virtual machine specifications.
当我们点击编译(Compile)时，它就会按照以太坊虚拟机(Ethereum Virtual Machine)的格式进行编译
We'll learn more about those specifications later.
我们会在以后学习更多关于这个格式的知识
And last, but not least, another huge congratulations on your first contract here.
最后，并且十分重要的是，恭喜你完成了你的第一份智能合约